

natalia_fuoco@hotmail.com +5493415593244 Linkedin: https://www.linkedin.com/in/nataliafuoc

GitHub: https://github.com/NFNat

I'm Developer full Stack Jr. Recently I discovered my passion for programming and I didn't hesitate for a moment to reinvent my professional career. I have worked 16 years in quality control in the pharmaceutical industry and I have a lot of GMP experience, teamwork and flexibility. This is for me the foundation for my professional future. Constant learning motivates me.

Professional Experience

July 2006 - July 2022

Quality Control Coordianator Synthon Argentina S.A.

Organization of laboratory tasks based on production needs.

Management of Raw Materials module in SAP and LIMS system

Analysis review and approval of raw materials, intermediate products, in-process controls, stability samples.

Management of analytical standards.

 $\label{thm:management} \mbox{Management of deviations, OOS (out of specification results) and exchange controls.}$

Control of compliance with GMP standards in the quality control laboratory.

Performance evaluation of the staff in charge.

Systems Management: LIMS, SAP, Empower, TrackWise, DocCompliance

November 2002 -December 2005 Laboratory Technician Toxicologia Integral Argentina S.A. (TIASA)

 $Preparation \ of samples \ for \ the \ determination \ of: pesticide \ residues, formulated \ products, solvents \ for \ industrial \ use \ by \ products \ product$

University of "Concepción del Uruguay", Argentina

 $Chromatography\ Gaseous\ (GLC),\ mycotoxins,\ amino\ acids\ by\ High\ Performance\ Liquid\ Chromatography\ (HPLC).$

Determination of metals by Atomic Absorption Spectrophotometry (AA)

Physical-chemical analysis of water and effluents and food.

Education

July 2022 - Present

Web Developer Full Stack in Programming Alura ONE, São Paulo/SP

Oracle Next Education F2T3, Programming

October 2021 - August

Web Developer Full Stack Jr in Programming INTI (Argentina Progrma), Argentina

Stack: Front end: HTML - CSS - JS-TS - Boostrap - Angular Back end: MySQL - Java - Spring Boot

March 2006 - December

2006

2022

Bachelor of Bromatology. in Food

Industry

Technology and Processing of Foods

Key Skills

- TeamWork
- Adaptability and Flexibility
- Productivity
- · Constant Learning
- Creative Thinking
- Proactivity

Languages

Spanish (native)

English C1 (Advanced)

Portuguese (Intermediate)